Welcome to the infantry.
The Pacifier is a comedy, family, action film directed by Adam Shankman.
Navy SEAL Shane Wolfe is handed a new assignment: Protect the five Plummer kids from enemies of their recently
deceased father -- a government scientist whose top-secret experiment remains hidden in the kids' house.
Shane Wolf, played by Vin Diesel.
Claire Fletcher, played by Lauren Graham.
Julie Plummer, played by Faith Ford.
Zoe Plummer, played by Brittany Snow.
Seth Plummer, played by Max Thieriot.
Lulu Plummer, played by Morgan York.
The Pacifier is a 2005 American family action comedy film directed by Adam Shankman,
written by Thomas Lennon and Robert Ben Garant and starring Vin Diesel.
After a failed rescue mission, Navy SEAL Shane Wolfe is
assigned as babysitter to the dead man's family.
The film was released on March 4, 2005 by Buena Vista Pictures Distribution.
It received generally negative reviews from critics.
It grossed $113 million in the United States and a total of $198.6
million worldwide against a budget of $56 million.
The film explores themes of mission, bodybuilder, body guard, scientist, family.
The tone is lighthearted.